# **LEWIS DONLEY**

FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### HTTPS://LEWISD1996.GITHUB.IO/LEWISDONLEY/

#### PROFILE -

I am graduate ready to put my experience, education and drive into my first position in the IT industry.

I've gained a vast amount of skills from university, in which I graduated with a first class honours in Computer Science, as well as the two years spent in China to work, travel and develop myself.

I am eager to learn, easy going by nature and enjoy working in a team, I also have a very high attention to detail.

I'm looking for a employer that I can progress and develop with, eventually helping me achieve my goal of becoming a Full Stack Developer.

## CONTACT

Address:

Blackrod Greater Manchester BL6 5RX

Phone:

07877313091

Email:

lewis.d1996@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

- + C#
- + Java
- + HTML/CSS (Sass)
- + ReactJS
- + Photoshop

#### **LANGUAGES**

- + English
- + Chinese 汉语

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

(2018 - 2020)

SIE Eduation, China, Shenzhen

Teacher

My duties included a wide range of taks preparing and delivering lessons, hosting events and taking part in school promotional material.

(2017 - 2018)

**Education First, China, Chengdu** 

Foreign Expert

As a foreign expert I was expected to plan and deliver high quality lessons, conduct teacher/parent meetings and carry out open lessons, during which I would teach while being observed by parents and managers.

### **EDUCATION**

(2014 - 2017)

University, MMU, UK

Bsc Hons Computer Science 1st Class Honours
Units taken include Advanced Programming,
Individual Project, Artificial Intelligence and
Data Structures & Algorithms.

(2012 - 2014)

College, Bolton Sixth Form College, UK A Level's

Computing, Business, Finance, Music Tech

(2007 - 2012)

School, Westhoughton High School, UK GCSE

Maths, English, Science etc.

#### **INTERESTS**













Fitness

Art

Music

Gaming

Football

Travel